Every time the rain no longer falls, and I
see the sky, I think the rain is falling.
Back to when I was a
child, who could only cry,
blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought,
one day I will be stronger.
Brideary and gratitude
fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was
before, or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure, but until
I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead!
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now!
Though time's all on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me!
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do!
The fiercest of all can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back!
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now!
Though time's not on our side,
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
What I hold dear away from me?
I know the future's there for us to see.
I think my poor heart is
about to go kabalooey!
Can't you slow us down somehow?
There's gotta be something!
What good old wax works
in a time like this?
Why are Luffy and the
others falling from the sky?
Good question.
To figure out what happened,
we'll have to go back in time.
The waves stopped moving.
How in the world did that happen?
That is messed up.
I mean, at least we're not dead.
But what are we supposed to do?
Take an ice pick to this thing.
I think I know who.
You did this as well.
Just take a look below.
The answer's clear enough.
It's the old man.
The battle's already started without us.
It's just as I thought.
I got an idea that'll get us down there.
We got less than three hours to work with,
so this is our best chance to
save Ace from getting executed.
Uh-huh, go on.
Are you mad?
You want to slide all the way down
this frozen wave back into the sea?
That's it.
But first, we gotta wiggle the ship
free so we can actually start sliding.
Need I remind you, this is a battleship.
It's not going to wiggle easily.
Did you hear that, you idiot?
If we work together, I know we can do it.
When you put it that way,
it sounds pretty cool.
Oh, right.
If Captain Buggy, the
next king of the pirates,
thinks we can do it,
then anything's possible.
His fighting spirit is rubbing off on us!
Buggy's the best captain ever! Yeah!
Attention all ships and soldiers.
A new target is T-O-T-T-Z.
Commence change in formation and
make the shift to Operation 3.
Sounds like the Navy is
busy giving out orders.
Advance all preparations now. Daddy?
What do you think that means?
Dunno.
Maybe some sort of secret
code they're using.
Once all soldiers are in place,
we will move the schedule forward
and execute Ace immediately.
That is all, Colby. No!
Luffy, no. Let's move!
There's no time for arguing.
We can't bum around any longer.
Everyone, follow Strawboy's
lead and help move this ship.
Let's go!
Wait a minute.
No!
Let's go on fly!
And that is how Luffy and the others
ended up falling from the sky.
Did that really happen?
A navy ship fell out of the
sky like it was nothing!
Water! It's water!
I thought we were dead!
I figured we'd all be goners once
the ship crashed into the ice.
Hey, why isn't it frozen here?
Gradrolls!
Start climbing! Ha!
This ain't got nothing on the water
torture we went through and impelled down!
What use are Devil Fruit
powers if you can't even swim?
Oh, my God.
LUMBAYS!
I'M HERE!
LUMBAY!
Finally found you!
Hey!
Is that who I think it is?
It's Crocodile!
And he's not the only one either!
Just take a look at that line up!
A who's who on both sides!
All the big names are here!
The world can't handle this madness!
Hey Ace, sit tight, okay?
Cause we're gonna get you out of here!
Hey Garth!
Your family's messing
things up again! Fluffy, no!
Look, Straw Hat's got some company!
It's Jinbei!
And the Revolutionary Army's at Bonkong!
There's a ton of infamous
pirates behind them too!
They must have all escaped
from Impel Down somehow!
Straw Hat's causing trouble again, is he?
I'm not surprised.
Is that Straw Hat?
What is Straw Hat Luffy doing here, too?
Looks like he forgot to bring
his crew along with him.
Luffy, I'm so relieved
to see that you're alive.
I can't believe it, Helmepo! What is it?
Not another surprise, I hope.
Straw Hat! That's crazy!
That means he must have
escaped from Impel Down!
How much tougher can this guy get?
Now those are some big
fish we're staring at.
Well, fancy seeing him.
That boy sure gets around, huh?
Guess that's the famous kid brother
Ace was always telling us about.
A former and active warlord hand in hand!
And look!
We even have the famous rookie
Straw Hat in attendance!
This is too good!
Smoker, look there!
Quickly!
Eat this!
Straw Hat Luthien Crocodile what are
those two doing together so it is him
The grandson of our very own Marine Hero
Guard and the son of
the Revolutionary Dragon
I'll make that boy regret the
day he decided to become a pirate
Of all things, you have the goal to
allow yourself a Straw Hat, Luffy.
After all we've done for you,
you're a payage like this!
That's right!
I choose to resign from
the seven warlords!
Rather peculiar, all these
groups uniting against us.
I highly doubt everyone here has
a common goal in this battle.
They're all too different
for that to make any sense.
Where'd Crocoboy go?
I guess the sucker chickened
out and left us high and dry.
Wait, there he is!
Damn it, you're supposed to wait for me!
It's Crocodile!
He's going straight for Whitebeard!
Long time no see, old man.
You never learn.
straw that knows too well what my strengths
and weaknesses are once you touch water
Then you can't turn into sand anymore.
You know, there's only
one reason I'm here.
If you want to save your brother
so bad, stay out of my way.
I'm killing Whitebeard
and you can't stop me.
So that old guy is Whitebeard.
I thought so.
Just stay away from him.
He's Ace's friend, so I'm not
going to let him get hurt.
Well, would you look at that?
It runs in the family.
Don't let him get close to Pops!
When you came back from
East Blue missing an arm,
you better believe the rumors were flying.
I was pretty curious myself.
Now I can ask you face to face, what
enemy did you give that left arm to?
Don't worry, I gave it to a kid.
Hey Squirt, that straw
hat that you're wearing,
it looks exactly like the one
red-haired Shanks used to have on him.
Hold on, how do you and
Shanks know each other?
You're right, it was his
hat, he left it to me.
Can you believe it pops look
this dork is my kid brother
You came here to rescue your
big brother, that's right.
Do you have the slightest idea
who our forces are up against?
A squirt like you is gonna
get slaughtered real easy.
Shut up, you don't know
you don't even know me?
I know what you're up to.
Yeah, you want to be the king, huh?
First, you've got to go
through me. Got it! Got it!
Got it!
Got it! Got it!
What a cheeky little punk.
Don't come crying to me for help if
you get a few boo-boos, spoiled brat.
Yeah, right.
I'm not all old like you.
I'm going to be the one to rescue Ace.
He's competing. With what?
We're done for.
How cute.
I would assume this is
all punishable by death.
Right, Sengoku?
Definitely.
They're throwing out the schedule
for an immediate execution.
Are you positive that's
what you heard them say?
Yeah, they said they got to get all
set for something first, though.
But I don't know what for,
because they were using codes.
I think you want to rescue Ace as bad
as me, and that's why I'm telling you.
Well, all right.
I suppose it's lucky I ran into you then.
Thanks, kiddo. Sure thing. No big deal.
Now he's talking like they're equals!
That boy has got some serious balls!
Right!
Hang on, Ace!
I'm on my way!
And there he goes.
Get out of my way.
Well, he's Ace's brother, all right!
Third division, let's get moving.
Keep up with the boy and
try to follow his lead.
Let's lend our support. What?
Come on!
14th Division!
Let's clear a path!
We're right behind you, boss!
Luffy.
One rookie daredevil
suddenly takes the lead
and they're acting like a whole new army.
Not that it matters.
Our strategy is airtight.
Don't hesitate!
Follow my orders!
So typical of Sengoku,
he probably doesn't
think the execution of a
mere pirate deserves the
formality of a schedule.
The big question is what they're
getting set up for first?
Hey Pops,
just in case you haven't heard,
word on the street is they're
expediting Ace's execution!
Straw Hat told me.
Something in my gut tells me Sengoku
wanted us to get that leaked info.
He wants us to advance. Huh?
That old bastard's too clever
to let his strategy get out.
Not that easily, at least.
He's many things, but not a fool.
Everybody climb!
A lightspeed kick?
Did you think I was gonna let you pass?
You fellas are awfully confident
for a bunch of nobodies. Damn!
It's Admiral Kizaru!
Huh?
Hey, you're that jerk from Saboori!
And you're the boy the Celestial
Dragons asked me to take care of.
Nice to get a second chance.
Crap!
Straw Hat's out of his boy!
Death win!
Ah, please!
I want to go home! What?
Whoa, Captain Buggy!
Wow, I knew you were gutted, but hot damn!
You mean you want to kill Kizaru, right?
So we can go home?
Yeah, these admirals aren't so tough.
All of the days work for Captain Buggy!
You're all delusional!
Would you quit enabling him?
Are you still breathing, straw boy?
You bet! Thanks, Eva! See ya! See ya?
Do you realize the only reason I'm
here is to save your rubber butt?
Damn, keys of the room.
Huh?
Wait, is that...
Cape!
Hey, that's the big guy that blew my
friends away and shot me across the sea!
Now rolling...
Bartholomew Kuma, you heartless scoundrel.
I understand you have a role
to play as warlord, but still,
all these years we've been friends,
and now you fire a laser at me?
Sorry, but your luck got away
from you when you ran into us.
Well, Straw Hat, might as well lie
down, because this is where you die.
Do I know you?
I'm full body.
I've been waiting a long time to make you
pay for what happened at the Baratirate.
Oh, right, Sanji kicked your ass there.
This Shigure.
I'm sure it'll ring a few bells for you.
Yeah, you're the hypno
guy from Usopp's village.
What are you doing with these guys?
I joined the Navy to hone my skills,
and I've mastered the art of hypnotism.
It's twice as effective
yielding two chakrams.
When I say one, two, Django,
you'll fall into a deep sleep.
One, two, Django!
Worthless sacks of crap.
So disappointing you're that
cage chick from Alabasta, right?
I don't have time to play
games with you people.
I never play games.
Come on, asleep? Cage?
Anyone who tries to pass through me will
be bound by the bars of my black cage.
I love it when she uses that line.
Captain Heena's the essence of I'm
done spending time behind bars! No!
Second gear!
So fast, I couldn't follow.
Hina failed.
You're not the only one who failed.
Captain Hina's truly taken us
captive now, both body and soul.
Just die!
Why do they all have to be so strong?
Ha!
Look at him go.
He's as high-spirited
as ever I see. Oh, yeah.
I can cut off his shadow again and
then plant it inside the new zombie.
Rise my zombie soldiers, it's time!
Now are you listening good capture
Straw Hat and bring them to me.
I want him alive
I don't want to deal with that creep now
You keep up!
There are more of them! Of course!
We are standing on a battlefield.
I've got plenty of fresh
corpses scattered about
to pick and choose from
Capture Straw Hat Luffy!
He's the one that caused that jailbreak!
That's right, keep going!
This should be enough
officers to keep the kid busy.
He can't keep bouncing
around like that forever.
Luffy...
Luffy, stay back!
What the hell do you think you're doing
you became a pirate because I wanted to!
You only went to sea
because you were following
me but I've got my own damn
life without you in it!
I've already got enough of my own friends!
Ace You get it?
I want you to stay the hell away
from me You really want to save me?
A scrawny wimp like you?
What makes you think I'd even
want something like that, huh?
That's just humiliating.
Go home, Luffy!
I didn't ask for this.
I beg you, please?
Ace, I can't let you die here with me.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
Ace!
You're my brother!
It's the truth.
All it takes to become
brothers is to share some sake.
From here on out, we're
honest-to-goodness brothers
Did I just hear them say
that they're brothers?
So then he's also Roger's son?
But both of these says Paris were dead
when he was born That can't be possible,
can't it?
I don't give a damn what you want!
I'm here to save you!
You stubborn jackass!
Move out, zombie soldiers!
Attack and capture!
Seawater!
Jinbei!
They came from Devil Fruit powers,
and thus, they are weak to the sea.
Press on.
These zombies will prove no match for me.
If you're sure.
First son of the sea, Jinbe.
We've got to fight a warlord.
Get out of here!
Wait,
you're making a mockery of the Navy by
letting this rookie take control of things.
Let me at him.
I'll crush this squirt into paste.
Make no mistake, he's a
tooth red in the making.
He was raised alongside
Firefist Ace as his stepbrother.
And if that's not bad enough, he's the
biological son of the revolutionary dragon.
Did he just say what I think he said?
He's the son of the worst
criminal in history.
Makes you think twice
about who you punch, huh?
Why didn't anyone tell me that's his dad?
Now they know.
Oh, man.
Luffy, it wouldn't bother me if
your father was the devil himself.
I had no idea.
Well, damn.
Okay!
GUMGUM PISTOL!
I finally understand what
happened at Log Town.
It only makes sense that
Dragon would save his own son.
Did you hear what he just said?
Does he meet the dragon head office?
Can you hear me?
I'm calling from Sabo.
I've got huge news.
We're talking worldwide headlines here.
I guess we'll just have to kill him too.
Who cares?
There's no reason to hide it any longer.
And it's not like it's
gonna make his life any
worse since he's already
a notorious outlaw.
You two brothers are both damn fools.
Dirt gear!
Now come, come!
Dying!
Cipher!
Release!
Say whatever means stuff you want!
I'm still gonna save you!
Oh hell yeah.
Your brother speaks for
every one of us Ace!
Yeah, we're all a part of your family too!
And nothing's gonna stop us!
Hey Marco, don't let that
kid die no matter what.
You got it.
Luffy